[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company was the first to introduce the consumer camcorder in 1983?", "correct_answer": "Sony", "incorrect_answers": ["Panasonic", "JVC", "Canon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Pirates of the Caribbean, Jack Sparrow intended to pick up a crew in Tortuga.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Peking Man is an example of what species of the genus Homo?", "correct_answer": "Homo erectus", "incorrect_answers": ["Homo sapiens", "Pithecanthropus", "Homo habilis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Israel?", "correct_answer": "Jerusalem", "incorrect_answers": ["Tel Aviv", "Kabul", "Islamabad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Anna Paquin is all grown up and stars in 2009s Margaret. It is directed and written by the writer of both Gangs of New York and Analyze This.  Who is this director?", "correct_answer": "Kenneth Lonerman", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Day-Lewis", "John Singleton", "August Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Aconcagua the tallest mountain in North America?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Beginning in the 1970s, author Stephen King re-popularized the horror novel. Which of the following novels was NOT written by King?", "correct_answer": "Hideaway", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrie", "Salems Lot", "The Dead Zone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these songs does Lilly start singing to the inmates of the prison in the 2003 movie The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "Swing Low, Sweet Chariot", "incorrect_answers": ["Amazing Grace", "His Eye Is on the Sparrow", "Oh Happy Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the usual size range of mature ants?", "correct_answer": "From 0.75 to 52 millimeters", "incorrect_answers": ["From 1.5 to 12 millimeters", "From 3.5 to 61 millimeters", "From 2 to 33 millimeters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the sixth largest island in the world, and the largest island that is entirely in Indonesia.", "correct_answer": "Sumatra", "incorrect_answers": ["New Guinea", "Java", "Borneo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the cottonmouth?", "correct_answer": "Snake", "incorrect_answers": ["Mouse", "Bat", "Lizard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny Crawford released an album in 1995.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]